export default [
{
            id: 1,
            question: 'What is 20 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['37','39','38','40'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is 20 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['41','40','38','39'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 3,
            question: 'What is 20 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['40','41','39','42'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 4,
            question: 'What is 20 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['43','40','41','42'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 5,
            question: 'What is 20 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['44','42','43','41'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 6,
            question: 'What is 20 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['45','42','44','43'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 7,
            question: 'What is 20 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['45','43','46','44'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 8,
            question: 'What is 20 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['46','45','44','47'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is 20 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['46','48','45','47'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 10,
            question: 'What is 20 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['46','48','49','47'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 11,
            question: 'What is 21 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['38','40','41','39'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 12,
            question: 'What is 21 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['41','39','40','42'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 13,
            question: 'What is 21 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['40','43','42','41'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 14,
            question: 'What is 21 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['42','44','41','43'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 15,
            question: 'What is 21 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['45','43','44','42'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 16,
            question: 'What is 21 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['45','44','43','46'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 17,
            question: 'What is 21 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['47','44','46','45'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 18,
            question: 'What is 21 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['45','46','47','48'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 19,
            question: 'What is 21 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['47','48','49','46'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 20,
            question: 'What is 21 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['48','50','49','47'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 21,
            question: 'What is 22 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['39','41','42','40'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 22,
            question: 'What is 22 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['42','41','43','40'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 23,
            question: 'What is 22 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['41','43','42','44'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 24,
            question: 'What is 22 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['45','42','43','44'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 25,
            question: 'What is 22 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['46','43','44','45'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 26,
            question: 'What is 22 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['45','46','44','47'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 27,
            question: 'What is 22 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['48','47','46','45'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 28,
            question: 'What is 22 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['46','48','47','49'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 29,
            question: 'What is 22 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['47','48','49','50'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 30,
            question: 'What is 22 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['49','51','50','48'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 31,
            question: 'What is 23 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['40','43','41','42'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 32,
            question: 'What is 23 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['41','44','42','43'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 33,
            question: 'What is 23 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['44','45','43','42'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 34,
            question: 'What is 23 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['46','43','44','45'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 35,
            question: 'What is 23 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['46','45','44','47'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 36,
            question: 'What is 23 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['45','47','48','46'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 37,
            question: 'What is 23 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['46','48','47','49'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 38,
            question: 'What is 23 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['48','50','47','49'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 39,
            question: 'What is 23 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['49','50','48','51'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 40,
            question: 'What is 23 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['49','52','51','50'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 41,
            question: 'What is 24 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['41','43','42','44'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 42,
            question: 'What is 24 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['43','44','45','42'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 43,
            question: 'What is 24 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['43','45','44','46'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 44,
            question: 'What is 24 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['47','46','45','44'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 45,
            question: 'What is 24 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['45','46','47','48'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 46,
            question: 'What is 24 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['46','48','49','47'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 47,
            question: 'What is 24 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['48','49','47','50'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 48,
            question: 'What is 24 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['50','48','49','51'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 49,
            question: 'What is 24 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['52','50','49','51'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 50,
            question: 'What is 24 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['51','52','53','50'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 51,
            question: 'What is 25 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['44','42','43','45'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 52,
            question: 'What is 25 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['45','46','44','43'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 53,
            question: 'What is 25 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['45','44','46','47'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 54,
            question: 'What is 25 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['46','45','48','47'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 55,
            question: 'What is 25 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['49','46','47','48'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 56,
            question: 'What is 25 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['50','48','47','49'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 57,
            question: 'What is 25 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['49','48','51','50'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 58,
            question: 'What is 25 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['51','49','52','50'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 59,
            question: 'What is 25 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['51','52','50','53'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 60,
            question: 'What is 25 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['51','53','54','52'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 61,
            question: 'What is 26 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['43','44','45','46'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 62,
            question: 'What is 26 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['47','44','45','46'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 63,
            question: 'What is 26 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['47','48','45','46'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 64,
            question: 'What is 26 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['49','47','48','46'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 65,
            question: 'What is 26 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['48','49','47','50'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 66,
            question: 'What is 26 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['48','51','49','50'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 67,
            question: 'What is 26 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['50','51','52','49'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 68,
            question: 'What is 26 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['52','51','53','50'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 69,
            question: 'What is 26 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['54','51','53','52'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 70,
            question: 'What is 26 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['52','55','54','53'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 71,
            question: 'What is 27 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['45','47','46','44'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 72,
            question: 'What is 27 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['48','47','46','45'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 73,
            question: 'What is 27 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['47','46','48','49'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 74,
            question: 'What is 27 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['49','48','50','47'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 75,
            question: 'What is 27 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['48','51','50','49'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 76,
            question: 'What is 27 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['52','51','49','50'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 77,
            question: 'What is 27 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['51','53','50','52'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 78,
            question: 'What is 27 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['51','54','53','52'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 79,
            question: 'What is 27 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['52','54','53','55'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 80,
            question: 'What is 27 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['53','54','56','55'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 81,
            question: 'What is 28 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['46','48','47','45'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 82,
            question: 'What is 28 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['46','47','49','48'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 83,
            question: 'What is 28 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['50','49','47','48'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 84,
            question: 'What is 28 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['48','51','49','50'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 85,
            question: 'What is 28 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['52','50','49','51'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 86,
            question: 'What is 28 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['53','51','52','50'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 87,
            question: 'What is 28 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['54','53','52','51'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 88,
            question: 'What is 28 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['55','53','54','52'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 89,
            question: 'What is 28 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['53','54','56','55'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 90,
            question: 'What is 28 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['57','56','55','54'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 91,
            question: 'What is 29 + 20 ?',
            answers: ['49','46','48','47'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 92,
            question: 'What is 29 + 21 ?',
            answers: ['50','47','49','48'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 93,
            question: 'What is 29 + 22 ?',
            answers: ['48','51','49','50'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 94,
            question: 'What is 29 + 23 ?',
            answers: ['50','52','51','49'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 95,
            question: 'What is 29 + 24 ?',
            answers: ['52','50','53','51'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 96,
            question: 'What is 29 + 25 ?',
            answers: ['54','51','52','53'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 97,
            question: 'What is 29 + 26 ?',
            answers: ['54','52','53','55'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 98,
            question: 'What is 29 + 27 ?',
            answers: ['53','54','55','56'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 99,
            question: 'What is 29 + 28 ?',
            answers: ['54','56','55','57'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 100,
            question: 'What is 29 + 29 ?',
            answers: ['56','58','57','55'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
]
